...\Experience\

Started as a gameplay programmer making pc and mobile game prototypes and quickly transition to porting games for the Nintendo Switch, improving my optimization and code reading skills.

Developed my producer, team managing and leadership skills by being in charge of a team developing Nintendo Switch titles and ports.

Also experienced with VR and modding, used to understand and integrate into ongoing projects.

Right now I'm trying to find inner peace

Work experience

- Lead Programmer @ Semaeopus

Jun 2023 - Present

From developing/porting WebGL applications, improving on existing projects and learning about blockchain and open source game servers

Lua, WebGL, C#, Go (Golang), linux

- Lead Port Programmer @ Nerd Monkeys

May 2019 - Oct 2021 / Jan 2022 - Jun 2023

Started as a internship, transitioned to a junior role and ended as a lead programmer

Managed teams, helped produce own IP titles, worked in cross-platform development, created tools and prototypes.

Unity, Game Maker Studio, Unreal, C#, JavaScript, C++

- Gameplay Programmer @ Red Cat Pig

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

Started as a internship, transitioned to a junior role and ended as a lead programmer

Managed teams, helped produce own IP titles, worked in cross-platform development, created tools and prototypes.

Unity, Game Maker, Unreal, C#, javascript, C++

- Being a Human

1998 - today

It's under NDA

Skills

- Software

Version Control

Project Management

and Collaboration

Game Maker Studio

Unreal

•••••

- Languages

C#
C++

Lua

JavaScript

Go (Golang)

Education

- ETIC_Algarve

Higher National Diploma - Videogames

Game Design, 2D Art, C# in Unity, Advanced programming, Spriting and Animations, Design and interfaces, Production and marketing, project management

- Escola Secundária Tomás Cabreira

Specializec Artistic Course in Communication Design

Adobe suite, blender, cinema 4D, brand creation, graphic design, video editing and editorial skills.

Languages

Native Portugues and fluent English

